<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Export generator="Cache" version="25" zv="Cache for Windows (x86-64) 2015.1 (Build 429U)" ts="2015-07-31 11:56:30">
<Class name="Controllers.Sample">
<Description><![CDATA[
Starting set of actions. This is the page controller called if the route is empty 
(meaning the top of the site). Login and redirection after logout are also handled here.

  <p>Copyright (c) 2011 James W "Bill" Westley-Farrell</p>

  <p>Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  You may obtain a copy of the License at</p>

      <p><a href=http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">Apache License 2.0</a>

  <p>Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  limitations under the License.</p>]]></Description>
<Super>EasyCSP.Controller.Base</Super>
<TimeChanged>63590,71386.184482</TimeChanged>
<TimeCreated>63460,66127.990758</TimeCreated>

<Property name="layout">
<Type>%String</Type>
<Final>1</Final>
<InitialExpression>"Site"</InitialExpression>
</Property>

<UDLText name="T">
<Content><![CDATA[
/*
Method afterConstruct() as %Boolean
{
} 
*/
]]></Content>
</UDLText>

<Method name="accessRules">
<Description>
The afterConstruct event will be run by the application automatically immediately
after the desired controller has been instantiated. Minimally, the access rules for
each action should be set up. That is, each user-facing view controller must set 
access rules for each action the controller will perform.

The accessRules method, if it exists, will be called automatically by the controller
base class to add access rules to the controller's environment. Specify the actions
as a comma-separated string of simple action names.</Description>
<ReturnType>%Status</ReturnType>
<Implementation><![CDATA[
	// allow any user access to help screens, the forgot password screen, the reset password screen,
	// the error display page, and the signon dialogue.
	do ..addAccessRule("allow", "index", "*")
	
	// Allow only logged in users sign off.
	do ..addAccessRule("allow", "create,update", "@")
	
	// Any other action is implicitly denied.
	
	quit $$$OK
]]></Implementation>
</Method>

<UDLText name="T">
<Content><![CDATA[
/*
                         Actions
*/
]]></Content>
</UDLText>

<Method name="actionBeforeIndex">
<ReturnType>%Boolean</ReturnType>
<Implementation><![CDATA[	quit 1
]]></Implementation>
</Method>

<Method name="actionIndex">
<ReturnType>%Boolean</ReturnType>
<Implementation><![CDATA[	quit 1
]]></Implementation>
</Method>
</Class>
</Export>
