<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Export generator="Cache" version="25" zv="Cache for Windows (x86-64) 2015.1 (Build 429U)" ts="2015-07-31 11:56:32">
<Class name="EasyCSP.Validator.Base">
<Description><![CDATA[
<p>Abstract class that positively identifies a validation rule as a validator object.
All classes that extend the base rule must adhere to two restrictions: first, the
code that performs the validation must be contained in a class method called "run";
and second, each such class must also contain a parameter called "message". The
message parameter is used to create error messages that may displayed in the GUI
CRUD form.</p>

<p>Each extended class performs exactly one specific type of entry validation -- the run() method. The
result must return a %Boolean value of either 0 or 1 (fail or pass). The model class
calls validation by default on new, save, insert, and update. This behavior can be
be extended in the model by doing two things: first, name the scenario the name that the
application will be using (any string value except the empty string); and second add
or modify a rule to the set of validation rules in the attribute definition that
covers the new scenario.</p>

<p>Rule classes are always called statically. An object of validation rule is never instantiated.
This means that all methods in a rule class must be ClassMethods and properties will
not available.</p>

<p>
Each validator must also contain a parameter called "message" (lower-case, as shown here).
When validation doesn't pass (0 is returned) by the run() method the model's next job is
to get the value of this parameter.
</p>

<p>
Both the error message and the run method are abstracted in this base class. This prevents
the app from crashing due to a poorly-constructed validator.
</p>

  <p>Copyright (c) 2011 James W "Bill" Westley-Farrell</p>

  <p>Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  You may obtain a copy of the License at</p>

      <p><a href=http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">Apache License 2.0</a>

  <p>Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  limitations under the License.</p>]]></Description>
<Abstract>1</Abstract>
<Super>%RegisteredObject</Super>
<TimeChanged>63599,61767.697887</TimeChanged>
<TimeCreated>63462,41050.085167</TimeCreated>

<Parameter name="message">
<Type>%String</Type>
<Default>Please override this message by adding a "message" parameter to your validation class.</Default>
</Parameter>

<Method name="run">
<Description>
Each child class of this base rule must override this ClassMethod.</Description>
<Abstract>1</Abstract>
<ClassMethod>1</ClassMethod>
<ReturnType>%Boolean</ReturnType>
<Implementation><![CDATA[		q 1
]]></Implementation>
</Method>
</Class>
</Export>
